Guide to the Frank Logue Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Mayor
  - United Newhallville Organization (Box 14)
  - Newhallville-Dixwell (Box 14)
  - West Hills-Pine Street (Box 14)
  - West Rock (Box 14)
  - Westville (Box 14)
  - Wooster Square (Box 14)
  - Mayor-flowers (1) (Box 15)
  - Mayor-flowers (2) (Box 15)
  - Federal building project (Box 15)
  - Mayor-goals for New Haven (Box 15)
  - Mayor-thank you letters (Box 15)
  - Mayor correspondence, A-Z (Box 15)
  - Mayor-political correspondence (Box 15)
  - Ciarlone, A.N. (Box 15)
  - Carter, Jimmy (President) (Box 15)
  - Giaimo, R. (Box 15)
  - Grasso, E. (Box 15)
  - Dodd, C., Ribicoff, A. (Box 15)
  - Kennedy, E. (Box 15)
  - Moffett, Toby (Box 15)
  - Schaffer, Gloria, Weicker, Lowell (Box 15)
  - Mayor-cabinet (Box 15)
  - New Leaders Council (NLC) Arts Task Force (Box 16)
  - Pictures (Box 16)
  - Mayor-political correspondence (Box 16)
  - Correspondence regarding primary campaign, 1979 (Box 16)
  - Mayor-speeches (Box 16)
  - Speeches (Box 16)
  - Speeches (Box 16)
  - Mayor-budget statement to Board of Alderman (Box 16)
  - Mayor-Declaration of Independence-Fourth of July (Box 16)
  - Mayor-Dialogue '76 (Box 16)
  - Mayor-"Restoring Order by Restoring Work" (Box 16)
  - Mayor-"The Uses of Leo Power" (Box 16)
  - Mayor-"Testimony on Welfare" (Box 16)
  - Mayor-State of the City (Box 16)
  - 181st Annual Chamber of Commerce Dinner (Box 16)
  - Holiday message (Box 16)
  - Mayor-Testimony-1976 General Assembly's (Box 16)
  - Transportation Hearing regarding Long Island Sound (Box 16)
  - Mayor-Introduction-Book by T.Hendricks & W. Goetzemen (Box 16)
  - Mayor-Inauguration (Box 16)
  - Mayor-Inauguration-Audience (Box 16)
  - Mayor-Inauguration (Box 16)
  - Mayor-Inauguration-Speech (Box 16)
  - Mayor-Inauguration-thank yous (Box 16)
  - Mtg-file (Box 16)
- Neighborhood Naturalist Program (Box 16)
- People Acting for Change (Box 16)
- People Acting for Change (2) (Box 16)
- Neighborhoods (Box 16)
- Neighborhood Housing Services (Box 16)
- Neighborhood Strategy Areas (Box 16)
- Parking Authority
  - Parking Authority (Box 16)
  - Parking Authority (Box 16)
  - Parking Department (Box 17)
  - Parking reports (Box 17)
  - Parking reports-Chapel Square garage (Box 17)
  - Parking Department (Box 17)
  - Parking Department-draft (Box 17)
  - Parking Department-Crown Street garage (Box 17)
  - Art Center garage (Box 17)
  - State Street garage (Box 17)
- Parks
  - Parks (Box 17)
  - Parks Department, 1979 (Box 17)
  - Park Department-budget hearing (Box 17)
  - Park Commission (1) (Box 17)
  - Park Commission (2) (Box 17)
  - Park Commissioners (Box 17)
  - Park Department (Box 17)
  - Park Department (Box 17)
  - Park Department-horticulture division (Box 17)
  - Park Department-budget (Box 17)
  - Park Department-Edgerton Park bridge (Box 17)
  - Park and Recreation (Box 17)
  - Park and Recreation-roller skating rink (Box 17)
  - Parks Department-Bowen Field (Box 17)
  - Parks and Recreation: field study (Box 17)
  - Parks and Recreation annual report (Box 17)
  - Parks and Recreation (Box 17)
  - Urban Park and Recreation Recovery (Box 17)
  - Parks and Recreation-Outline, 1978 (Box 17)
  - Edgewood Park (Box 17)
  - Fairmont Park (Box 17)
  - Theatre-in-the-Park (Box 17)
  - Pension study (Box 17)
- Police
  - Police department (2) (Box 17)
  - Police department-case/incident reports (Box 17)
  - Police department-crime (Box 17)
  - Police department (1) (Box 17)
  - Police department-general (Box 17)
  - Police department chief (Box 17)
  - Police department chief deputy (Box 17)
  - Police department resumes (Box 17)
  - Police department-"Quality of Education" (Box 17)
  - Police-full-time (Box 17)
  - Police department (1) (Box 17)
  - Police-part-time (Box 17)
  - Police-budget (Box 17)
  - Police-school liaison program (Box 17)
  - Police department (5) (Box 18)
  - Police training (Box 18)
  - Police union (Box 18)
  - Police department-applications (Box 18)
  - Police department-applications (2) (Box 18)
  - Police-boat (Box 18)
  - New Haven police boat (Box 18)
  - Police Commissioners, Board (Box 18)
  - Police Commissioners (Box 18)
  - Police Commissioners, Board (1) (Box 18)
  - Police Commissioners, Board (2) (Box 18)
  - Police Commissioners, Board (3) (Box 18)
  - Police Commissioners, Board (4) (Box 18)
  - Police-wiretapping (Box 18)
  - Police department regarding correspondence (general) (Box 18)
  - Police department regarding correspondence (general), 1979 (Box 18)
  - Police department regarding correspondence (general), 1978 (Box 18)
  - Police department regarding correspondence (general) (Box 18)
  - Police department regarding correspondence (general), 1977 (Box 18)
  - Police department regarding correspondence (general), 1976 July-December (Box 18)
  - Police department regarding correspondence (general) (Box 18)
  - Police department regarding correspondence (general), 1976 January-June (Box 18)
  - Police department regarding correspondence (general), 1974-1975 (Box 18)
  - Police-residency ordinance (Box 18)
  - News releases (8) (Box 19)
  - Public information (4) (Box 19)
  - Police Department-Victims Services Unit (Box 19)
  - Police (Box 19)
  - Police department-planning unit (Box 19)
  - Police-personnel (Box 19)
  - Police-corruption (Box 19)
  - Police department regarding report "Police Manpower Study" by Charles Rogovin, 1977 (Box 19)
- Policy analysis, office (Box 19)
- Policy analysis, office (Box 19)
- Public Information (Box 19)
  - Public Information (Box 19)
  - News releases, 1976 January-March (Box 19)
  - News releases, 1976 March (Box 19)
  - News releases, 1976 April (Box 19)
  - News releases, 1976 May-June (Box 19)
  - News releases, 1976 July (Box 19)
  - News releases, 1976 August (Box 19)
  - Proclamations (Box 19)
  - Proclamations (Box 19)
  - Proclamations (2) (Box 19)
  - Media (Box 19)
  - Media (Box 19)
  - Media representatives (Box 19)
  - Media representatives (1) (Box 19)
  - Media representatives (2) (Box 19)
  - Media representatives (3) (Box 19)
  - Media representatives (4) (Box 19)
  - News conferences (Box 19)
  - News conferences (Box 19)
  - News releases (Box 20)
  - News releases (Box 20)
  - News releases (1) (Box 20)
  - Statements (Box 20)
  - Public information (1) (Box 20)
  - News releases (2) (Box 20)
  - News releases (Box 20)
  - News releases (3) (Box 20)
  - News releases (4) (Box 20)
  - Public information-proclamation (Box 20)
  - Public information-citizens' office hours (Box 20)
  - Public information-channel 3 (Box 20)
  - Media campaign (Box 20)
  - Public information-general (Box 20)
  - Public information-WELI Radio (Box 20)
  - WAVZ (Box 20)
  - Public information (2) (Box 20)
  - News releases (4) (Box 20)
  - News releases (5) (Box 20)
  - News releases (Box 20)
  - Public information (3) (Box 20)
  - News releases (6) (Box 20)
  - Public information (5) (Box 21)
  - Citizens' office hours (Box 21)
  - Public information-response (Box 21)
  - Public information (1) (Box 21)
  - Public information (2) (Box 21)
  - Public information-Latino youth (Box 21)
- Public Works
  - Public works (Box 21)
  - Public works (1) (Box 21)
  - Public works, 1979 (Box 21)
  - Public works-springcleaning program (Box 21)
  - Public works (2) (Box 21)
  - Public works-director (Box 21)
  - Public works-sewer construction (Box 21)
- Purchasing Department
  - Purchasing department (Box 21)
  - Purchasing department (Box 21)
  - Purchasing agent (Box 21)
  - Purchasing department (Box 21)
  - Bureau of Purchases (Box 21)
- Redevelopment
  - Redevelopment (1) (Box 21)
  - Redevelopment-East Pizza (Box 21)
  - Redevelopment-meetings, 1976 April-May (Box 21)
  - Redevelopment (2) (Box 21)
  - Redevelopment (4) (Box 22)
  - Redevelopment-Whalley Avenue (Box 22)
  - Redevelopment Liveable Cities Grant (Box 22)
  - Redevelopment-vacant buildings (Box 22)
  - Redevelopment-general (Box 22)
  - Land disposition agreement (Box 22)
  - Redevelopment Agency regarding correspondence (Box 22)
  - Redevelopment Agency, 1979 (Box 22)
  - Redevelopment Agency regarding minutes of meetings, 1979 (Box 22)
  - Redevelopment Agency (NH) regarding special fund, 1979 (Box 22)
  - Redevelopment Agency meetings (Box 22)
  - Redevelopment (5) (Box 22)
  - Redevelopment-general (2) (Box 22)
  - Redevelopment Agency, 1978 (Box 22)
  - Redevelopment Agency, 1977 (Box 22)
  - Redevelopment-meeting minutes (Box 22)
  - Neighborhood presentation: Fair Haven (Box 22)
  - Redevelopment: home weatherization financial statements (Box 22)
  - Housing Conservation & Code Enforcement Agency (Box 22)
  - Redevelopment (Box 22)
  - Housing Code Enforcement Agency (Box 22)
  - Inner City Co-Op Farm (Box 23)
  - Redevelopment regarding neighborhood preservation-(Office of), 1979 (Box 23)
  - Neighborhood preservation (Box 23)
  - Redevelopment Neighborhood preservation (Box 23)
  - Neighborhood preservation (Box 23)
- Registrar of Voters
  - Registrar of Voters (Box 23)
  - Registrar of Voters (Box 23)
  - Residency, 1979 (Box 23)
  - Residency (Box 23)
  - Residency Review Board (Box 23)
  - Residency law (Box 23)
- Retirement Board
  - Retirement Board, New Haven (Box 23)
  - Retirement Board, New Haven (Box 23)
  - Retirement Board, staff (Box 23)
  - Staff (Box 23)
  - Retirement fund, staff (Box 23)
- Staff-holidays vacations (Box 23)
- Staff-resumes (Box 23)
- Taxes
  - Tax appeals-Yale (Box 23)
  - Taxes-bonds (Box 23)
  - Tax Collector (Box 23)
  - Taxes-general (Box 23)
  - Tax reform-taxable bonds (Box 23)
  - Board of Tax Review (Box 23)
- Phasing-In (Box 23)
- Local revenue diversification (Box 23)
- Traffic and Parking
  - Traffic and parking (Box 23)
  - Traffic and parking, 1979 (Box 23)
  - Traffic and parking-complaints (Box 23)
  - Traffic and parking-operations (Box 23)
  - Traffic and parking-general (Box 24)
  - Traffic and parking-pedestrian thoroughfares in downtown New Haven (Box 24)
  - Traffic and parking-intersection of College Street and Frontage Road (Box 24)
  - Traffic Authority (Box 24)
  - Traffic Authority (Box 24)
  - Traffic Authority agenda (Box 24)
  - Traffic Authority, 1979 (Box 24)
  - Transit Study (Box 24)
  - New Haven Transit District (Box 24)
  - Transit District (New Haven), 1979 (Box 24)
  - Transit (1) (Box 24)
  - Transit (2) (Box 24)
  - Transit-bus shelters (Box 24)
  - New Haven bus shelters (Box 24)
- Transition Office
  - Transition office (Box 24)
  - Newly elected mayors-seminar on (Box 24)
  - Transition & Leadership (Box 24)
  - Transition, 1979 November-December (Box 24)
- Vital statistics (Box 24)
- Vital statistics (Box 24)
- Weights and Measures (Box 24)
- Weights and Measures (Box 24)
- Welfare
  - Welfare director (Box 24)
  - Welfare (Box 24)
  - Welfare department (2) (Box 24)
  - Department of Welfare correspondence (Box 24)
  - Department of Welfare fraud report (Box 24)
- Zoning Appeals Board (Box 24)
- Zoning Appeals Board (Box 24)
- Arts
  - Arts-Miscellaneous (Box 25)
  - Arts-Miscellaneous (2) (Box 25)
  - Arts Center (Box 25)
  - Arts Center-Audubon Street (Box 25)
  - Art in City Hall (Box 25)
  - Mayor Logue (Box 25)
  - Arts Council (Box 25)
  - Arts-Culture Affairs Commission (Box 25)
  - Arts-Institute Cultural Affairs (Box 25)
  - Arts-Inner Theatre (Box 25)
  - Arts-Long Wharf (Box 25)
  - Arts, National Endowment for the, National Urban Conference on the Arts (Box 25)
  - Hunanities, National Endowment for the (Box 25)
  - Arts and Hunanities, National Endowment for the (Box 25)
  - Arts-Job I (Box 25)
  - Arts-Music (Box 25)
  - Chamber Orchestra of New England (Box 25)
  - Arts-New Haven Opera Theatre (Box 25)
  - New Haven Symphony (Box 25)
  - Arts-Dance (Box 25)
- Banks (Box 25)
- Banks-miscellaneous (Box 25)
- Commission-historical (Box 25)
- Commission on Equal Opportunities (Box 25)
- Commission Human Rights and Equal Opportunity (Box 25)
- Commission Safety (Box 26)
- Commission of Pharmcy (Box 26)
- Commission-Connecticut Justice (Box 26)
- Commission Gaming-Off-Trackbetting (OTB) (Box 26)
- Commission Status of Women (Box 26)
- Commission Gaming-general (Box 26)
- Commission retirement (Box 26)
- Commission State Elections (Box 26)
- Corporations
  - Corporations (Box 26)
  - Corporations-Armstrong Rubber (Box 26)
  - Corporations-Earmark, Inc. (Box 26)
  - Corporations-Edw. Malley Co. (Box 26)
  - Corporations-Gas Co. (Box 26)
  - Corporations-Time, Life (Box 26)
  - M. Schiavone & Sons (Box 26)
  - Schiavone Realty (Box 26)
  - Corporations-United Illuminating (Box 26)
  - Corporations-United Illuminating (Box 26)
  - Corporations-United Illuminating (Box 26)
- Public hearing (Box 26)
- Water Company (Box 26)
  - Water Company-general (1) (Box 26)
  - Water Company-general (2) (Box 26)
  - Water Company-meetings (Box 26)
  - Water Company-background to September 1976 (Box 26)
  - Water Company-general (3) (Box 26)
  - Water Company-feasibility study (Box 27)
  - Water Company-feasibility-final report (Box 27)
  - Water Company-R.W. Beck contract (Box 27)
  - Water Company-reorganization (Box 27)
- Foundations
  - Foundation, police (Box 27)
  - Foundations (Box 27)
  - Foundation, Egerton (Box 27)
  - Foundation, Ford (Box 27)
  - Foundation, Shirley Frank (alcoholism) (Box 27)
  - Foundation, Edw. W. Hazen (Box 27)
  - Foundation, International Rowing Course (Box 27)
  - Foundation, New Haven (Box 27)
  - Foundation-Hudson, Dayton (Box 27)
- Historic Districts
  - Historic District-Lowell (Box 27)
  - Fair Haven Historic District Commission (Box 27)
  - Dwight Historic Study (Box 27)
  - New Haven Historic District Commission (Box 27)
  - Quinnipiac Historic District (Box 27)
  - Historic District Commission (Box 27)
- Hospital
  - Hospital (Box 27)
  - Hospital-St. Raphael (Box 27)
  - Hospital: Yale-New Haven (Box 27)
  - Yale-New Haven Hospital (Box 27)
  - Hospitals-Yale Cost Commission (Box 27)
- Parades and Festivals
  - Parades (Box 27)
  - Parades-Columbus Day (Box 27)
  - Fair Haven Festival (Box 27)
  - Festival on the Green-New Haven (Box 27)
  - Parades-Freddy Fixer (Box 27)
  - Parades-Martin Luther King (Box 27)
  - Parades-Memorial Day (Box 27)
  - Parades-Puerto Rican Day (Box 27)
  - Parades-St. Patrick's Day (Box 27)
  - Parades-Salute to Israel (Box 27)
  - Parades-United Nations Day (Box 27)
  - Parades Veterans Day (Box 27)
- United States Government
  - United States Army, Department (Box 28)
  - United States Coast Guard (Box 28)
  - United States Coast Guard- Eagle (Box 28)
  - United States Commerce, Department (Box 28)
  - United States Commerce, Department-public works (Box 28)
  - United States Commerce, Department-Employment Act, 1976 (Box 28)
  - Department of Commerce-standard (Box 28)
  - Metropolitan Statistical Areas (SMSA) (Box 28)
  - United States Defense, Department of (Box 28)
  - United States Health, Education, and Welfare (Box 28)
  - United States Education, Department (Box 28)
  - Urban Development Action Grant (UDAG) (Box 28)
  - Task Force on Force (Box 28)
  - U.S. Department of Housing and Urban Development (HUD)-State Street projects (Box 28)
  - U.S. Department of Housing and Urban Development (HUD)-legislation (Box 28)
  - Newhallville-Dixwell Urban Development Act Grant (Box 28)
  - U.S. Department of Housing and Urban Development (HUD)-Section 8 (Box 28)
  - Housing and Urban Development (HUD) (Deparment of) State regarding correspondence (Box 28)
  - U.S. Department of Housing and Urban Development (HUD)-Connecticut-004-001 (Box 28)
  - U.S. Department of Housing and Urban Development (HUD)-Section 816 (Box 28)
  - U.S. Department of Housing and Urban Development (HUD)-Comprehensive Planning Assistance Grants (Box 28)
  - U.S. Department of Housing and Urban Development (HUD)-Hill Central Homes Project (Box 28)
  - U.S. Department of Housing and Urban Development (HUD)-Model Cities Program (Box 28)
  - U.S. Department of Housing and Urban Development (HUD)-People Acting for Change (PAC) (Box 28)
  - Section 312 Rehabilitation Loan Program (Box 28)
  - U.S. Department of Housing and Urban Development (HUD)-Regional Rehabilitation Insurance (Box 28)
  - U.S. Department of Housing and Urban Development (HUD)-National Housing Act (Box 28)
  - U.S. Department of Housing and Urban Development (HUD)-Block Grant Evaluation (Box 28)
  - 82-84 Fourth Street-U.S. Department of Housing and Urban Development (HUD) (Box 28)
  - Bella Vista-working conditions (Box 28)
  - U.S. Department of Housing and Urban Development (HUD)-Relocation and Real Property A (Box 28)
  - U.S. Department of Housing and Urban Development (HUD)-Neighborhood Strategy Program (Box 28)
  - U.S. Department of Housing and Urban Development (HUD)-Connecticut Report on Relocation Monitoring (Box 28)
  - United States House of Representatives (Box 28)
  - U.S. Department of Housing and Urban Development (HUD)-Oriental Gardens (Box 28)
  - United States Postal Services (Box 28)
  - U.S. Department of Housing and Urban Development (HUD)-correspondence (Box 28)
  - U.S. Department of Housing and Urban Development (HUD)-Bella Vista (Box 28)
  - Anti-Inflaction Plan (Box 28)
  - Congress (Box 28)
  - Task Force on Economic Growth (Box 28)
  - United States Federal Budget (Box 28)
  - United States Congressional Committees (Box 28)
  - United States Environmental Protection Agency (Box 28)
  - United States Housing and Urban Development (1) (Box 28)
  - United States Housing and Urban Development (2) (Box 28)
  - United States Housing and Urban Development-community Development Block Program (Box 28)
  - Sub-committee-United States Intergovernmental (Box 28)
  - Relations and Human Resources (Box 28)
  - Commission-United States Productivity and Work Quality (Box 28)
  - United States National Manpower Administration (Box 28)
  - Commission-United States Civil Service (Box 28)
  - United States Senate (Box 28)
  - United States Interior, Department (Box 28)
  - United States Justice, Department (Box 28)
  - United States Labor, Department (Box 28)
  - United States Transportation, Secretary (Box 28)
  - Municipal Bonds Municipal Finance (Box 28)
  - United States White House (Box 28)
  - White House-Urban Policy (Box 28)
  - United States Senate Municipal Bonds (Box 28)
  - U.S. Department of Housing and Urban Development (HUD)-Antillean Manor (Box 28)
- Connecticut State Department of
  - Administrative Services, Department (Box 29)
  - State of Connecticut Department on Ageing (Box 29)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station (Box 29)
  - Department of Children & Youth Services-foster care payment (Box 29)
  - Community Affairs (Box 29)
  - Community Affairs, Department (Box 29)
  - Connecticut Community Services Administration Ivan Ashley Meeting (Box 29)
  - Consumer Counsel, Office (Box 29)
  - Correction (Box 29)
  - Correction Department (Box 29)
  - Education (Box 29)
  - Education Department (Box 29)
  - Environmental Protection (Box 29)
  - Connecticut Environmental Advisory Council (Box 29)
  - Environmental Protection, Department (Box 29)
  - Solid Waste (Box 29)
  - Connecticut Environmental Protection Agency (EPA)-Clean Water Act (Box 29)
  - Connecticut Environmental Protection Agency (EPA)-solid waste (Box 29)
  - Department of Environmental Protection (DEP) Middletown Avenue incinerator (Box 29)
  - Connecticut Department of Environmental Protection (DEP)-Waste Water Treatment Report (Box 29)
  - Solid Waste-Milford (Box 29)
  - Connecticut Sewer Facility Plan, 1979 (Box 29)
  - Sewer charges-East Haven Hamden (Box 29)
  - Sewer use charges-Department of Environmental Protection (DEP) (Box 29)
  - Department of Environmental Protection (DEP)-sewer department organization (Box 29)
  - Department of Environmental Protection (DEP)-East Shore Park (Box 29)
  - United States Department of Environmental Protection (Box 29)
  - East Shore Waste Treatment Plant Grant Agreement (Box 29)
  - East Shore Water Waste Pollution Control Plant (Box 29)
  - WPAP Project-71-75-1 (Box 29)
  - East Shore WPAP Project (Box 29)
  - WPAP Project-71-74-1 (Box 29)
  - East Shore Water Waste Treatment Plant (Box 29)
  - Department of Finance and Control (Box 29)
  - Finance Committee (Box 29)
  - Finance, revenue and bonding (Box 29)
  - General Assembly (Box 29)
  - Connecticut House of Representatives (Box 29)
  - Connecticut Health, Department (Box 29)
  - Connecticut Council on Human Resources (Box 29)
  - Department of Human Resources (Box 29)
  - Labor (Box 29)
  - Connecticut Labor Department (1) (Box 29)
  - Connecticut Labor Department (2) (Box 29)
  - Connecticut Mental Health Department (Box 29)
  - Connecticut Military Department (Box 29)
  - Connecticut Personnel Department (Box 29)
  - Policy and Management, Office (Box 29)
  - Public Utilities Control Authority (Box 29)
  - Connecticut revenue sharing (Box 29)
  - Rivers, harbors and bridges (Box 29)
  - Rivers (Box 29)
  - Harbors (Box 29)
  - Port of New Haven (Box 29)
  - New Haven harbor (Box 29)
  - New Haven harbor-pollution (Box 29)
  - New Haven harbor-City Point (Box 29)
  - New Haven harbor-dredging (Box 29)
  - Connecticut harbormaster (Box 29)
  - New Haven harbor-development (Box 29)
  - New Haven harbor (Box 29)
  - Bridges (Box 29)
  - Connecticut bridges-Boulevard (Box 29)
  - Connecticut Forbes Avenue bridge (Box 29)
  - Connecticut Grand Avenue bridge (Box 29)
  - Connecticut Temple Street bridge (Box 29)
  - Connecticut Tomlinson bridge (Box 29)
  - Long Island bridge (Box 29)
  - Poughkeepsie Railroad bridge (Box 29)
  - Connecticut Social Services Department (Box 29)
  - Connecticut Tax Collector (Box 29)
  - Transportation (Box 30)
  - Connecticut Department of Transportation (DOT)-Route 34 (2) (Box 30)
  - Route 34 (Box 30)
  - Department of Transportation (DOT)-ground transportation centers (Box 30)
  - Connecticut Department of Transportation (DOT)-Route 34 (3) (Box 30)
  - Department of Transportation (DOT)-handicapped transport (Box 30)
  - Department of Transportation (DOT) handicapped transportation (Box 30)
  - Connecticut Department of Transportation (DOT)-taxi cabs (Box 30)
  - Department of Transportation (DOT)-House Bill (HB) 7027 Transportation Committee (Box 30)
  - Department of Transportation (DOT)-New Haven Transit District (Box 30)
  - Connecticut Transit Operators (Box 30)
  - Department of Transportation (DOT): Blatchley Avenue Over Railroad (Box 30)
  - Department of Transportation (DOT): general correspondence (Box 30)
  - Connecticut Department of Transportation (DOT) (1) (Box 30)
  - Connecticut Department of Transportation (DOT) (2) (Box 30)
  - Department of Transportation (DOT): Federal Highway Safety Program (Box 30)
  - Connecticut Transportation Department (3) telephone numbers (Box 30)
  - Connecticut Transportation Plan, 1974 (Box 30)
  - Connecticut Transportation Department (3) (Box 30)
  - Connecticut Department of Transportation-buses, bus shelters (Box 30)
  - Department of Transportation (DOT): New Haven Railroad Station (Box 30)
  - Department of Transportation (DOT): New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad (Box 30)
  - Connecticut Department of Transportation (DOT)-Pennsylvania Central (Box 30)
  - Department of Transportation (DOT): general (Box 30)
  - Connecticut Department of Transportation (DOT)-Route 34 (Box 30)
  - Connecticut Department of Transportation (DOT)-Totalisator (Box 30)
  - Office of Treasurer Governor Grasso's proposed budget (Box 30)
  - Treasurer, Office (Box 30)
  - New Haven Urban Ssytems Project: 92-231, 92-224 (Box 30)
- A (Box 31)
- Aetna World Cup (Box 31)
- Albie Booth Memorial Boys Club (Box 31)
- Alcohol (Box 31)
- Alcohol Council of Greater New Haven (Box 31)
- American Industry of Religion (Box 31)
- American Postal Workers Union AFL-CIO (Box 31)
- Amtrak (Box 31)
- Architects (Box 31)
- B (Box 31)
- Babe Ruth League (Box 31)
- Basset Properties (Box 31)